https://makeway.org/about-us/policies/website-privacy-policy/

MakeWay Foundation
MakeWay Foundation (The Foundation) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Website Privacy Statement explains the manner in which The Foundation collects, uses and discloses certain non-personal information through our website located at www.makeway.org (the “Website”). Please refer to our general Privacy Policy for information on how we may collect, use and disclose personal information.
Use of Website
You may access and use the Website without providing any personal information whatsoever with respect to yourself to The Foundation.
Non-Identifiable Information Collected
The Website automatically collects certain non-identifiable information regarding website usage, such as which pages you visited and the date and time of the visit. Your non-identifiable information may be disclosed to others and stored permanently for future use. We use Google Analytics to improve our website content and design. Additional information on how Google uses data can be found at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners.
Cookies
The website uses “cookies”. Cookies are data which may be stored on your computer so as to allow your web browser to remember something about a website. Cookies can be of assistance in remembering passwords, so you do not have to enter it every time you log on to a website. Cookies may be temporary (automatically deleted when the user logs off the website) or permanent (stored on the user’s computer until manually deleted by the user). Most website browsers allow users to reject or disable website cookies.
Other Websites
The Website may contain links to other websites or internet resources. When you click on one of those links you are contacting another website or internet resources that may collect information about you voluntarily or through cookies or other technologies. The Foundation has no responsibility or liability for or control over those other websites or internet resources or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.
Changes to Website Privacy Statement
If we decide to change this Website Privacy Statement, we will post the changed version on the Website so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Comments or Questions
If you have any questions or comments about this Website Privacy Statement, please contact our Privacy Officer at:
400 – 163 West Hastings Street
Vancouver, BC V6B 1H5
Telephone: 604-647-6611
Sign up for updates and stories of community-led transformation and systems change from across the MakeWay community.
You can unsubscribe at any time via link in our emails.
Read our Website Privacy Policy to learn more about how we take care of your information.
Name*
First Name
Last Name
Email Address*
NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
VANCOUVER
400-163 W Hastings St.
400-163 W Hastings St.
thriving together.
Policies Contact Charitable Registrations
Nature and communities
thriving together.
We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By browsing this website, you agree to our use of cookies.
Accept
